<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Women &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product-tag/women/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 04:22:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/logo.png</url>
	<title>Women &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Colorful Knitwear Combo Set</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/colorful-knitwear-combo-set/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/colorful-knitwear-combo-set/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex items-start overflow-x-auto whitespace-pre-wrap break-words flex-col gap-4">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">

Stay cozy and chic with our vibrant multi-color gloves and matching topi (hat) in the Colorful Knitwear Combo Set.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Easy to Style</li>
 	<li>* Texture and Softness</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elevate your winter style with our Colorful Knitwear Combo Set. This delightful set includes a pair of cozy gloves and a matching topi (hat), both hand-knitted in a beautiful array of multi-colors. The gloves provide warmth and dexterity, while the topi adds a touch of charm to your winter ensemble. Crafted with attention to detail and made from soft, high-quality yarn, this set ensures comfort and durability. With its vibrant and eye-catching design, the Colorful Knitwear Combo Set is the perfect choice to brighten up your cold weather look and keep you snug all season long. Embrace the joy of matching accessories and make a fashion statement with this stunning combination of multi-colored knitwear.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/colorful-knitwear-combo-set/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tailored Perfection Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/tailored-perfection-knit-topi/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/tailored-perfection-knit-topi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A beautifully designed woolen topi with one tail pointing up and two tails at the bottom, showcasing machine-made craftsmanship and stylish elegance.
<ul>
 	<li>* Stylish and Fashionable</li>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* All-Day Comfort</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the beauty of machine-made craftsmanship with this exquisite woolen topi. Featuring a stunning design, this topi showcases one upward-pointing tail and two tails at the bottom, adding a touch of elegance and flair. The intricate detailing and fine stitches reflect the dedication put into creating this piece. Crafted from soft and warm wool, it provides both comfort and style. Embrace the allure of this tailored masterpiece and elevate your winter wardrobe with the Tailored Perfection Knit Topi.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/tailored-perfection-knit-topi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Floral Elegance Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/floral-elegance-knit-topi/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/floral-elegance-knit-topi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=331</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A white woolen topi adorned with intricate red flower designs and a playful pom-pom ball on top, combining elegance, charm, and whimsy in a cozy winter accessory.
<ul>
 	<li>Handcrafted Beauty</li>
 	<li>Cozy and Soft</li>
 	<li>Made of Natural Fibers</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exude elegance and charm with this woolen knitted topi in pristine white. Adorned with intricate red flower designs, this topi beautifully captures the essence of nature&#8217;s blossoms. The whimsical touch of a pom-pom ball perched atop adds a playful and delightful element. Crafted with care and attention to detail, this topi offers both style and warmth. The soft and cozy wool material keeps you comfortable during colder days, while the combination of white, red, and the pom-pom ball adds a touch of whimsy and sophistication. Embrace the beauty of nature with the Floral Elegance Knit Topi, a perfect accessory to elevate your winter ensemble.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/floral-elegance-knit-topi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mountain Majesty Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/mountain-majesty-knit-topi/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/mountain-majesty-knit-topi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A cozy brown woolen topi with a captivating mountain design, bringing the beauty of nature and warmth to your winter style.
<ul>
 	<li>*  100% Wool</li>
 	<li>*  Timeless Style</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Excellence</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace the majestic allure of the mountains with this woolen knitted topi in a rich brown color. The intricate design showcases the silhouette of snow-capped peaks, capturing the essence of nature&#8217;s grandeur. Crafted with care and attention to detail, this topi offers both style and warmth. The soft and cozy wool material keeps you comfortable during colder days, while the earthy brown shade adds a touch of rustic charm. Whether you&#8217;re exploring the outdoors or simply seeking a cozy accessory, the Mountain Majesty Knit Topi is a perfect choice to evoke the spirit of adventure and nature&#8217;s beauty.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/mountain-majesty-knit-topi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cozy Circlet Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-circlet-knit-beanie/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-circlet-knit-beanie/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This round, woolen headwear is designed to keep you cozy and stylish during colder days. With its intricate knit pattern and snug fit, the Cozy Circlet Knit Topi adds a touch of warmth and fashion to your outfit, making it the perfect accessory for chilly weather.
<ul>
 	<li>* Authentic Product</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Excellence</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace warmth and style with the Cozy Circlet Knit Topi. Crafted from soft and woolen yarn, this round headwear is designed to keep you snug during chilly days. The intricate knit pattern forms a textured and comfortable fit, while the stretchy material ensures a perfect circumference. With its versatile round shape, this topi offers a fashionable touch to any outfit. Whether you&#8217;re enjoying outdoor adventures or simply strolling around town, the Cozy Circlet Knit Topi is a must-have accessory for those seeking both comfort and style.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-circlet-knit-beanie/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ice Chill Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/ice-chill-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/ice-chill-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay warm and stylish with these cozy gloves made from soft, warm wool. Embrace the cool vibes with the Ice Chill Knit Gloves and keep your hands cozy in icy temperatures.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Classic and Timeless</li>
 	<li>* All-Day Comfort</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stay warm and stylish with the Ice Chill Knit Gloves. These soft and cozy gloves are made from warm wool to keep your hands snug in the cold. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the snug fit and ribbed cuffs ensure a comfortable and secure wear. Whether you&#8217;re walking in the snow or running errands, these gloves are the perfect winter accessory. Embrace the frosty vibes with the Ice Chill Knit Gloves and enjoy the chilly season with style.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/ice-chill-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/whispering-breeze-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/whispering-breeze-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that cocoon your hands in comfort. Embrace the soothing whisper of the breeze with the Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves.
<ul>
 	<li>* Exceptional Quality</li>
 	<li>* Luxurious Texture</li>
 	<li>* Sustainable and Eco-friendly</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace the gentle caress of the Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves. Made from soft and warm wool, these gloves offer a cozy and comfortable fit for your hands. The delicate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and snug wear. Whether you&#8217;re exploring the winter wonderland or simply running errands, these gloves will keep your hands protected from the cold while adding a stylish flair to your outfit. Experience the soothing whisper of the breeze with the Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves and enjoy the warmth and sophistication they bring to your winter days.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/whispering-breeze-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winter Whispers Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whispers-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whispers-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 06:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that embrace your hands with gentle comfort. The delicate knit pattern adds an elegant touch, while the ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and cozy fit. Experience the whisper of winter with the Winter Whispers Knit Gloves.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Cozy and Soft</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your hands in the gentle embrace of the Winter Whispers Knit Gloves. These cozy and stylish gloves are crafted from soft and warm wool, providing ultimate comfort during the chilly months. The delicate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the ribbed cuffs offer a secure and snug fit. Whether you&#8217;re strolling through snow-covered streets or enjoying outdoor activities, these gloves will keep your hands protected and fashionably chic. Experience the whisper of winter with the Winter Whispers Knit Gloves, a must-have accessory for the season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whispers-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Embrace a world of color with these vibrant woolen gloves. With their cozy and warm construction, these gloves provide both comfort and style. Make a statement with the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves and brighten up your winter ensemble.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Styling</li>
 	<li>* Warmth and Insulation</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Step into a world of color and creativity with the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves. These gloves are a vibrant mix of hues that come together in an abstract and mesmerizing pattern. Crafted from soft and cozy wool, they provide exceptional warmth and comfort for your hands during the colder months. The unique and eye-catching design makes them a statement accessory that adds a pop of excitement to any winter ensemble. The snug fit and ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and comfortable wear, while the durable construction guarantees long-lasting use. Whether you&#8217;re running errands or enjoying outdoor activities, the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves are the perfect companions, combining style and functionality seamlessly. Embrace the cosmic fusion of colors and elevate your winter style with these captivating knit gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that wrap your hands in comforting bliss. Embrace the cozy comfort and chic style of the Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves, the perfect accessory for the winter season.
<ul>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* Timeless Style</li>
 	<li>* Perfect Fit</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your hands in the harmonious blend of softness and style with these blue mix woolen gloves. The mesmerizing blend of blue hues adds a touch of sophistication, while the cozy knit fabric keeps your hands warm and protected. With their versatile design and comfortable fit, these gloves are perfect for adding a pop of color to your winter ensemble. Step into a world of comfort and style with the Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
