<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Men &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product-tag/men/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 04:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/logo.png</url>
	<title>Men &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Colorful Knitwear Combo Set</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/colorful-knitwear-combo-set/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/colorful-knitwear-combo-set/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex items-start overflow-x-auto whitespace-pre-wrap break-words flex-col gap-4">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">

Stay cozy and chic with our vibrant multi-color gloves and matching topi (hat) in the Colorful Knitwear Combo Set.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Easy to Style</li>
 	<li>* Texture and Softness</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elevate your winter style with our Colorful Knitwear Combo Set. This delightful set includes a pair of cozy gloves and a matching topi (hat), both hand-knitted in a beautiful array of multi-colors. The gloves provide warmth and dexterity, while the topi adds a touch of charm to your winter ensemble. Crafted with attention to detail and made from soft, high-quality yarn, this set ensures comfort and durability. With its vibrant and eye-catching design, the Colorful Knitwear Combo Set is the perfect choice to brighten up your cold weather look and keep you snug all season long. Embrace the joy of matching accessories and make a fashion statement with this stunning combination of multi-colored knitwear.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/colorful-knitwear-combo-set/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emerald Oasis Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/emerald-oasis-knit-topi/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/emerald-oasis-knit-topi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A green woolen Muslim cap crafted with soft and breathable materials, featuring an intricate knit pattern for an elegant and comfortable headwear option.
<ul>
 	<li>* Authentic Product</li>
 	<li>* All-Day Comfort</li>
 	<li>* Classic and Timeless</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Step into an oasis of style with the Emerald Oasis Knit Topi. This green woolen cap is specially designed for the Muslim community, offering a comfortable and fashionable headwear option. Crafted with soft and breathable materials, it ensures a cozy fit while allowing for breathability. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance and sophistication, making it a perfect accessory for religious and cultural occasions. Embrace the beauty of tradition with the Emerald Oasis Knit Topi, a stylish and comfortable choice for Muslim individuals seeking a distinctive headwear option.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/emerald-oasis-knit-topi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tailored Perfection Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/tailored-perfection-knit-topi/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/tailored-perfection-knit-topi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A beautifully designed woolen topi with one tail pointing up and two tails at the bottom, showcasing machine-made craftsmanship and stylish elegance.
<ul>
 	<li>* Stylish and Fashionable</li>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* All-Day Comfort</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the beauty of machine-made craftsmanship with this exquisite woolen topi. Featuring a stunning design, this topi showcases one upward-pointing tail and two tails at the bottom, adding a touch of elegance and flair. The intricate detailing and fine stitches reflect the dedication put into creating this piece. Crafted from soft and warm wool, it provides both comfort and style. Embrace the allure of this tailored masterpiece and elevate your winter wardrobe with the Tailored Perfection Knit Topi.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/tailored-perfection-knit-topi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mountain Majesty Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/mountain-majesty-knit-topi/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/mountain-majesty-knit-topi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A cozy brown woolen topi with a captivating mountain design, bringing the beauty of nature and warmth to your winter style.
<ul>
 	<li>*  100% Wool</li>
 	<li>*  Timeless Style</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Excellence</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace the majestic allure of the mountains with this woolen knitted topi in a rich brown color. The intricate design showcases the silhouette of snow-capped peaks, capturing the essence of nature&#8217;s grandeur. Crafted with care and attention to detail, this topi offers both style and warmth. The soft and cozy wool material keeps you comfortable during colder days, while the earthy brown shade adds a touch of rustic charm. Whether you&#8217;re exploring the outdoors or simply seeking a cozy accessory, the Mountain Majesty Knit Topi is a perfect choice to evoke the spirit of adventure and nature&#8217;s beauty.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/mountain-majesty-knit-topi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cozy Circlet Knit Topi</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-circlet-knit-beanie/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-circlet-knit-beanie/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This round, woolen headwear is designed to keep you cozy and stylish during colder days. With its intricate knit pattern and snug fit, the Cozy Circlet Knit Topi adds a touch of warmth and fashion to your outfit, making it the perfect accessory for chilly weather.
<ul>
 	<li>* Authentic Product</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Excellence</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace warmth and style with the Cozy Circlet Knit Topi. Crafted from soft and woolen yarn, this round headwear is designed to keep you snug during chilly days. The intricate knit pattern forms a textured and comfortable fit, while the stretchy material ensures a perfect circumference. With its versatile round shape, this topi offers a fashionable touch to any outfit. Whether you&#8217;re enjoying outdoor adventures or simply strolling around town, the Cozy Circlet Knit Topi is a must-have accessory for those seeking both comfort and style.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-circlet-knit-beanie/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Embrace a world of color with these vibrant woolen gloves. With their cozy and warm construction, these gloves provide both comfort and style. Make a statement with the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves and brighten up your winter ensemble.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Styling</li>
 	<li>* Warmth and Insulation</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Step into a world of color and creativity with the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves. These gloves are a vibrant mix of hues that come together in an abstract and mesmerizing pattern. Crafted from soft and cozy wool, they provide exceptional warmth and comfort for your hands during the colder months. The unique and eye-catching design makes them a statement accessory that adds a pop of excitement to any winter ensemble. The snug fit and ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and comfortable wear, while the durable construction guarantees long-lasting use. Whether you&#8217;re running errands or enjoying outdoor activities, the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves are the perfect companions, combining style and functionality seamlessly. Embrace the cosmic fusion of colors and elevate your winter style with these captivating knit gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that wrap your hands in comforting bliss. Embrace the cozy comfort and chic style of the Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves, the perfect accessory for the winter season.
<ul>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* Timeless Style</li>
 	<li>* Perfect Fit</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your hands in the harmonious blend of softness and style with these blue mix woolen gloves. The mesmerizing blend of blue hues adds a touch of sophistication, while the cozy knit fabric keeps your hands warm and protected. With their versatile design and comfortable fit, these gloves are perfect for adding a pop of color to your winter ensemble. Step into a world of comfort and style with the Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cozy Haven Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-haven-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-haven-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=248</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay cozy and chic with these soft and warm woolen gloves, perfect for embracing the beauty of the winter season. Soft and warm woolen accessories to keep your hands stylishly cozy all winter long.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Handmade with Love</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Accessory</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the ultimate comfort and warmth with the Cozy Haven Knit Gloves. Crafted from soft and luxurious wool, these gloves are designed to keep your hands snug and cozy during the colder months. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance and visual interest, making them a stylish accessory to complement any winter outfit. The ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and comfortable fit, while providing an extra layer of insulation against chilly winds. Whether you&#8217;re taking a leisurely stroll or engaging in outdoor activities, these gloves offer the perfect balance of flexibility and warmth. With their versatile design and timeless appeal, the Cozy Haven Knit Gloves are the ideal companion for both casual and formal occasions. Treat your hands to the soothing embrace of the Cozy Haven Knit Gloves and elevate your winter style with their cozy and chic allure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-haven-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snowflake Whisper Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/snowflake-whisper-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/snowflake-whisper-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=247</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cozy and chic white gloves that add an elegant touch to your winter look. Stay warm and stylish with these soft and luxurious white gloves, perfect for adding a touch of sophistication to your winter attire.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Handmade with Care</li>
 	<li>* Superior Warmth</li>
</ul>
<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">

&#160;
<div class="flex gap-1"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace winter&#8217;s beauty with these soft and cozy white gloves. The elegant design and warm woolen fabric keep your hands snug and stylish. Perfect for adding a touch of sophistication to your winter ensemble, these gloves are a must-have accessory for the snowy season. Stay cozy and chic with these soft and warm white gloves. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the woolen fabric keeps your hands snug and protected. The versatile white color complements any outfit, making them a perfect winter accessory. Embrace the beauty of winter with the Snowflake Whisper Knit Gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/snowflake-whisper-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frostbite Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frostbite-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frostbite-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=244</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories to shield your hands from the winter chill. The intricate knit pattern adds a stylish touch, while the snug fit ensures maximum comfort. Perfect for everyday wear, these gloves combine fashion and functionality. Stay cozy and chic with Frostbite Knit Gloves.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Beauty</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Introducing Frostbite Knit Gloves, your go-to winter accessories for ultimate warmth and style. Crafted from soft and cozy wool, these gloves provide a soothing cocoon for your hands in the cold weather. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance and visual interest, making them a fashionable statement piece. With their snug fit and ribbed cuffs, these gloves offer a secure and comfortable feel, keeping chilly drafts at bay. Whether you&#8217;re running errands or attending a special event, Frostbite Knit Gloves are the perfect companions, combining fashion and functionality seamlessly. Stay cozy, chic, and protected from the winter chill with these stylish knit gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frostbite-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
