<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Scarf &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product-category/scarf/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:02:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/logo.png</url>
	<title>Scarf &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Warmth Weaver Knitscarf</title>
		<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/warmth-weaver-knitscarf/</link>
					<comments>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/warmth-weaver-knitscarf/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/?post_type=product#038;p=131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Snuggle up in style with the Warmth Weaver Knitscarf, a cozy and versatile woolen accessory that adds a touch of warmth and charm to your winter wardrobe.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Warmth without Bulk</li>
 	<li>* Stylish and Versatile</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Warmth Weaver Knitscarf is a cozy and stylish woolen accessory that embraces you in comfort. Its soft and knitted texture adds a touch of warmth to your winter ensemble. With its versatile design and classic appeal, this scarf effortlessly complements any outfit. Whether worn loosely draped or wrapped snugly, the Warmth Weaver Knitscarf is a must-have for the cold season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/warmth-weaver-knitscarf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cozy Comfort Knitscarf</title>
		<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/cozy-comfort-knitscarf/</link>
					<comments>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/cozy-comfort-knitscarf/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/?post_type=product#038;p=129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A cozy and stylish woolen accessory that embraces you in warmth. Its soft texture and intricate knitting make it a delight to wear. With its neutral color, it effortlessly complements any outfit, adding a touch of sophistication. Wrap yourself in comfort and style with the Cozy Comfort Knitscarf.
<ul>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* Cozy and Insulating</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Beauty</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Indulge in the Cozy Comfort Knitscarf, a beautifully knitted woolen accessory that offers both warmth and style. The soft and plush texture provides a comforting feel against the skin, perfect for chilly days. With its versatile design and neutral color, this scarf effortlessly complements a variety of outfits. Whether wrapped snugly or draped loosely, the Cozy Comfort Knitscarf is a must-have for those seeking a cozy and fashionable winter accessory.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/cozy-comfort-knitscarf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crimson Ember Knitscarf</title>
		<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/crimson-ember-knitscarf/</link>
					<comments>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/crimson-ember-knitscarf/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/?post_type=product#038;p=124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A striking and luxurious red scarf that adds a touch of warmth and elegance to your winter attire. Crafted from soft wool, it offers both comfort and style for the colder months. Embrace the vibrant allure of the Crimson Ember Knitscarf and make a bold fashion statement.
<ul>
 	<li>* Travel-Friendly</li>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* Enduring Style</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ignite your winter style with the Crimson Ember Knitscarf, a captivating accessory that exudes warmth and sophistication. Made from soft and cozy red wool, this knitted scarf adds a bold pop of color to your cold-weather ensemble. The rich crimson hue beautifully complements a variety of outfits, making it a versatile and eye-catching addition to your wardrobe. With its generous length and plush texture, the Crimson Ember Knitscarf provides both comfort and style. Whether worn draped loosely or wrapped snugly, this scarf is sure to turn heads and make a statement. Embrace the fiery allure of the Crimson Ember Knitscarf and elevate your winter fashion with its vibrant charm.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/crimson-ember-knitscarf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winter Frost Knitscarf</title>
		<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/winter-frost-knitscarf/</link>
					<comments>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/winter-frost-knitscarf/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 02:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/?post_type=product#038;p=122</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A gracefully knitted white scarf that embodies winter's tranquility. Crafted with softness and style in mind, it adds a touch of sophistication to any cold-weather ensemble. Wrap yourself in cozy elegance with this timeless accessory.
<ul>
 	<li>* Unisex Styles</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Designs</li>
 	<li>* Gift-Worthy</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex items-start overflow-x-auto whitespace-pre-wrap break-words flex-col gap-4">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Wrap yourself in the pure elegance of the Winter Frost Knitscarf, a beautifully crafted accessory that exudes timeless charm. Made from soft white wool, this knitted scarf is perfect for embracing the winter season in style. The classic white color adds a touch of sophistication and versatility, effortlessly complementing any outfit. With its generous length and plush texture, the Winter Frost Knitscarf offers cozy warmth and endless styling options. Whether draped loosely or wrapped snugly, this scarf is a must-have accessory for those seeking both comfort and fashion-forward elegance.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="flex gap-1"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/winter-frost-knitscarf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rainbow Dreams Knitscarf</title>
		<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/rainbow-bliss-knitscarf/</link>
					<comments>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/rainbow-bliss-knitscarf/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 02:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/?post_type=product#038;p=121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A vibrant and cozy accessory, handcrafted with care. The mesmerizing rainbow pattern adds a burst of color to your winter style, making it a must-have for standing out and spreading joy. Perfect for gifting or brightening up your own winter wardrobe.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Authentic Product</li>
 	<li>* Winter Wardrobe Essential</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex items-start overflow-x-auto whitespace-pre-wrap break-words flex-col gap-4">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p><strong>Why to Choose Rainbow Dreams Knitscarf ???</strong></p>
<p><strong>1.Vibrant and Colorful:</strong> This Woollen knitted scarf features a mesmerizing rainbow pattern that adds a burst of vibrant colors to your winter ensemble.</p>
<p><strong>2.Cozy Warmth:</strong> Made from soft and warm wool, this scarf keeps you snug and comfortable during chilly days.</p>
<p><strong>3.Versatile Styling:</strong> The generous length and width of the Rainbow Bliss Knitscarf allow for various styling options, from wrapping it snugly around your neck to draping it loosely over your shoulders.</p>
<p><strong>4.Eye-catching Design:</strong> The intricate knit pattern creates a visually appealing texture that adds a touch of uniqueness to your look.</p>
<p><strong>5.Stand out from the Crowd:</strong> With its bold and lively rainbow colors, this scarf is sure to make you stand out and brighten up any outfit.</p>
<p><strong>6.Handcrafted with Care:</strong> Each Rainbow Bliss Knitscarf is carefully handmade, ensuring attention to detail and quality craftsmanship.</p>
<p><strong>7.Perfect for All Ages:</strong> Suitable for both adults and children, this scarf brings joy and cheerfulness to people of all ages.</p>
<p><strong>8.Winter Wardrobe Essential:</strong> A must-have accessory for the winter season, this rainbow scarf adds a pop of color and warmth to your cold-weather outfits.</p>
<p><strong>9.Great Gift Idea:</strong> Surprise your loved ones with this unique and delightful scarf, a thoughtful present for birthdays, holidays, or any special occasion.</p>
<p><strong>10.Spread Happiness:</strong> Embrace the positive energy and happiness that the Rainbow Bliss Knitscarf radiates, bringing joy wherever you go.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="flex gap-1"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/rainbow-bliss-knitscarf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silver Grey Knit scarf</title>
		<link>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/grey-mist-petite-knitscarf/</link>
					<comments>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/grey-mist-petite-knitscarf/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 02:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/?post_type=product#038;p=102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A stylish and cozy accessory in soft grey wool. Wrap yourself in elegance with the Grey Mist Petite Knitscarf, a small and charming accessory crafted from soft grey wool for a cozy and fashionable look.
<ul>
 	<li>* Handcrafted with Care</li>
 	<li>* Eye-catching Design</li>
 	<li>* Perfect for All Ages</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elevate your winter style with the Silver Grey Knitted scarf. Crafted from a soft and luxurious silver grey wool, this knitted accessory exudes a sense of refined elegance. The subtle shimmer in the fabric beautifully captures the essence of moonlight, adding a touch of enchantment to your look. The intricate knit pattern showcases meticulous craftsmanship, while the generous length and width provide versatility in styling. Whether draped effortlessly or wrapped snugly, this knit scarf is designed to keep you warm and fashionable. Step out into the winter night adorned in the captivating allure of the Silver Grey Knit scarf and embrace the magic it brings to your ensemble.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/jeenakarmi/OoniBunai.git/product/grey-mist-petite-knitscarf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
