<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Gloves &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product-category/gloves/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 04:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/logo.png</url>
	<title>Gloves &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ice Chill Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/ice-chill-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/ice-chill-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay warm and stylish with these cozy gloves made from soft, warm wool. Embrace the cool vibes with the Ice Chill Knit Gloves and keep your hands cozy in icy temperatures.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Classic and Timeless</li>
 	<li>* All-Day Comfort</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stay warm and stylish with the Ice Chill Knit Gloves. These soft and cozy gloves are made from warm wool to keep your hands snug in the cold. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the snug fit and ribbed cuffs ensure a comfortable and secure wear. Whether you&#8217;re walking in the snow or running errands, these gloves are the perfect winter accessory. Embrace the frosty vibes with the Ice Chill Knit Gloves and enjoy the chilly season with style.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/ice-chill-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/whispering-breeze-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/whispering-breeze-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that cocoon your hands in comfort. Embrace the soothing whisper of the breeze with the Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves.
<ul>
 	<li>* Exceptional Quality</li>
 	<li>* Luxurious Texture</li>
 	<li>* Sustainable and Eco-friendly</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace the gentle caress of the Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves. Made from soft and warm wool, these gloves offer a cozy and comfortable fit for your hands. The delicate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and snug wear. Whether you&#8217;re exploring the winter wonderland or simply running errands, these gloves will keep your hands protected from the cold while adding a stylish flair to your outfit. Experience the soothing whisper of the breeze with the Whispering Breeze Knit Gloves and enjoy the warmth and sophistication they bring to your winter days.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/whispering-breeze-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winter Whispers Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whispers-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whispers-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 06:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that embrace your hands with gentle comfort. The delicate knit pattern adds an elegant touch, while the ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and cozy fit. Experience the whisper of winter with the Winter Whispers Knit Gloves.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Cozy and Soft</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your hands in the gentle embrace of the Winter Whispers Knit Gloves. These cozy and stylish gloves are crafted from soft and warm wool, providing ultimate comfort during the chilly months. The delicate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the ribbed cuffs offer a secure and snug fit. Whether you&#8217;re strolling through snow-covered streets or enjoying outdoor activities, these gloves will keep your hands protected and fashionably chic. Experience the whisper of winter with the Winter Whispers Knit Gloves, a must-have accessory for the season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whispers-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Embrace a world of color with these vibrant woolen gloves. With their cozy and warm construction, these gloves provide both comfort and style. Make a statement with the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves and brighten up your winter ensemble.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Styling</li>
 	<li>* Warmth and Insulation</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Step into a world of color and creativity with the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves. These gloves are a vibrant mix of hues that come together in an abstract and mesmerizing pattern. Crafted from soft and cozy wool, they provide exceptional warmth and comfort for your hands during the colder months. The unique and eye-catching design makes them a statement accessory that adds a pop of excitement to any winter ensemble. The snug fit and ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and comfortable wear, while the durable construction guarantees long-lasting use. Whether you&#8217;re running errands or enjoying outdoor activities, the Cosmic Fusion Knit Gloves are the perfect companions, combining style and functionality seamlessly. Embrace the cosmic fusion of colors and elevate your winter style with these captivating knit gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosmic-fusion-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories that wrap your hands in comforting bliss. Embrace the cozy comfort and chic style of the Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves, the perfect accessory for the winter season.
<ul>
 	<li>* Superior Quality</li>
 	<li>* Timeless Style</li>
 	<li>* Perfect Fit</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your hands in the harmonious blend of softness and style with these blue mix woolen gloves. The mesmerizing blend of blue hues adds a touch of sophistication, while the cozy knit fabric keeps your hands warm and protected. With their versatile design and comfortable fit, these gloves are perfect for adding a pop of color to your winter ensemble. Step into a world of comfort and style with the Cosy Comfort Knit Gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cosy-comfort-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cozy Haven Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-haven-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-haven-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=248</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay cozy and chic with these soft and warm woolen gloves, perfect for embracing the beauty of the winter season. Soft and warm woolen accessories to keep your hands stylishly cozy all winter long.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Handmade with Love</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Accessory</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the ultimate comfort and warmth with the Cozy Haven Knit Gloves. Crafted from soft and luxurious wool, these gloves are designed to keep your hands snug and cozy during the colder months. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance and visual interest, making them a stylish accessory to complement any winter outfit. The ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and comfortable fit, while providing an extra layer of insulation against chilly winds. Whether you&#8217;re taking a leisurely stroll or engaging in outdoor activities, these gloves offer the perfect balance of flexibility and warmth. With their versatile design and timeless appeal, the Cozy Haven Knit Gloves are the ideal companion for both casual and formal occasions. Treat your hands to the soothing embrace of the Cozy Haven Knit Gloves and elevate your winter style with their cozy and chic allure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-haven-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snowflake Whisper Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/snowflake-whisper-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/snowflake-whisper-knit-gloves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=247</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cozy and chic white gloves that add an elegant touch to your winter look. Stay warm and stylish with these soft and luxurious white gloves, perfect for adding a touch of sophistication to your winter attire.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Handmade with Care</li>
 	<li>* Superior Warmth</li>
</ul>
<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">

&#160;
<div class="flex gap-1"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace winter&#8217;s beauty with these soft and cozy white gloves. The elegant design and warm woolen fabric keep your hands snug and stylish. Perfect for adding a touch of sophistication to your winter ensemble, these gloves are a must-have accessory for the snowy season. Stay cozy and chic with these soft and warm white gloves. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance, while the woolen fabric keeps your hands snug and protected. The versatile white color complements any outfit, making them a perfect winter accessory. Embrace the beauty of winter with the Snowflake Whisper Knit Gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/snowflake-whisper-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frostbite Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frostbite-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frostbite-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=244</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories to shield your hands from the winter chill. The intricate knit pattern adds a stylish touch, while the snug fit ensures maximum comfort. Perfect for everyday wear, these gloves combine fashion and functionality. Stay cozy and chic with Frostbite Knit Gloves.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Beauty</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Introducing Frostbite Knit Gloves, your go-to winter accessories for ultimate warmth and style. Crafted from soft and cozy wool, these gloves provide a soothing cocoon for your hands in the cold weather. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance and visual interest, making them a fashionable statement piece. With their snug fit and ribbed cuffs, these gloves offer a secure and comfortable feel, keeping chilly drafts at bay. Whether you&#8217;re running errands or attending a special event, Frostbite Knit Gloves are the perfect companions, combining fashion and functionality seamlessly. Stay cozy, chic, and protected from the winter chill with these stylish knit gloves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frostbite-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frosty Whisper Knit Gloves</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frosty-whisper-knit-gloves/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frosty-whisper-knit-gloves/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soft and warm woolen accessories to keep your hands stylishly cozy all winter long.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Excellence</li>
 	<li>* All-Day Comfort</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 bg-gray-50 dark:bg-[#444654]">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex items-start overflow-x-auto whitespace-pre-wrap break-words flex-col gap-4">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p>Embrace the chilly season with the Frosty Whisper Knit Gloves, a cozy and stylish accessory to keep your hands warm. Crafted from soft and warm wool, these gloves offer a luxurious feel and a snug fit. The intricate knit pattern adds a touch of elegance and visual interest to your winter ensemble. With their versatile design, the Frosty Whisper Knit Gloves complement a wide range of outfits, from casual to formal. The ribbed cuffs ensure a secure and comfortable fit, keeping the cold air out. Perfect for outdoor activities or daily commutes, these gloves provide both warmth and dexterity for your hands. Stay fashionably cozy this winter with the Frosty Whisper Knit Gloves, a must-have accessory for cold-weather comfort and style.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="flex justify-between lg:block">
<div class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="flex gap-1"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="group w-full text-gray-800 dark:text-gray-100 border-b border-black/10 dark:border-gray-900/50 dark:bg-gray-800">
<div class="flex p-4 gap-4 text-base md:gap-6 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] xl:max-w-3xl md:py-6 lg:px-0 m-auto">
<div class="flex-shrink-0 flex flex-col relative items-end">
<div class="w-[30px]">
<div class="relative flex"><img alt="" aria-hidden="true" /></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3 lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)]">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col gap-3">
<div class="min-h-[20px] flex items-start overflow-x-auto whitespace-pre-wrap break-words flex-col gap-4">
<div class="empty:hidden"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/frosty-whisper-knit-gloves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
