<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Legwarmer &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product-category/legwarmer/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 04:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/logo.png</url>
	<title>Legwarmer &#8211; OoniBunai</title>
	<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Color Splash Knitted Legwarmers</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/color-splash-knitted-legwarmers/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/color-splash-knitted-legwarmers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay warm and make a bold statement with our Color Splash Knitted Legwarmers. Hand-knitted with vibrant colors, they add a playful pop to any outfit, while keeping your legs cozy and stylish.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* All-Season Comfort as it's easy to style</li>
 	<li>* Sustainable Fashion</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elevate your style and keep your legs cozy with our Color Splash Knitted Legwarmers. Handcrafted with care, these woolen legwarmers feature a delightful blend of vibrant colors, creating a captivating and eye-catching design. Made from soft and insulating wool, they provide warmth and comfort during colder days. The stretchy ribbed cuffs ensure a secure fit, while the length extends to just below the knee, offering both style and functionality. Whether you&#8217;re dancing, attending outdoor events, or simply adding a pop of color to your everyday look, our Color Splash Knitted Legwarmers are the perfect accessory. Embrace their playful charm and enjoy the comfort and fashion they bring to your legs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/color-splash-knitted-legwarmers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>KnitWool Legwarmer</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/knitwool-legwarmer/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/knitwool-legwarmer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 09:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay cozy and chic with our KnitWool Legwarmer. Crafted from soft and warm wool, these knitted legwarmers provide comfort and style for the colder seasons.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Warmth in Cold Weather</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Styling</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elevate your winter style with our KnitWool Legwarmer. Crafted from soft and warm wool, these knitted legwarmers offer both comfort and fashion. The intricate knitting pattern adds a touch of sophistication, while the stretchy material ensures a perfect fit. Stay cozy and chic during colder days with our KnitWool Legwarmer, the ideal accessory for keeping your legs stylishly warm.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/knitwool-legwarmer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Woolen Comfort Legwarmer</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/woolen-comfort-legwarmer/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/woolen-comfort-legwarmer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 09:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Wrap your legs in warmth and style with our Woolen Comfort Legwarmer Duo. Crafted from soft and insulating wool, these knitted legwarmers provide cozy comfort and a fashionable touch for colder days.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Handcrafted Beauty</li>
 	<li>* Versatile Styling</li>
</ul>
&#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your legs in cozy comfort with our Woolen Comfort Legwarmer Duo. Crafted from soft and insulating wool, these knitted legwarmers offer a snug and warm fit. The stylish design adds a touch of charm, while the stretchy material allows for easy movement. Whether you&#8217;re lounging at home or venturing out, our Woolen Comfort Legwarmer Duo is the perfect accessory to keep you comfortably fashionable throughout the winter season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/woolen-comfort-legwarmer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CozyKnit Woolen Legwarmer</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozyknit-woolen-legwarmer/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozyknit-woolen-legwarmer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 08:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Embrace comfort and style with our knitted legwarmers. Crafted from soft wool, they provide cozy warmth and a fashionable touch for any outfit.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Stylish and Versatile</li>
 	<li>* Warmth without Bulk</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wrap your legs in warmth and style with our CozyKnit Woolen Legwarmers. Crafted from soft and insulating wool, these knitted legwarmers offer a comfortable and snug fit. Perfect for chilly days, they provide an extra layer of coziness to keep your legs toasty. Whether you&#8217;re lounging at home or stepping out, our CozyKnit Woolen Legwarmers are the perfect accessory to add a touch of comfort and fashion to your winter wardrobe.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozyknit-woolen-legwarmer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winter Whisper Legwarmer</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whisper-legwarmer/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whisper-legwarmer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 08:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Luxurious knitted wool legwarmers that offer unparalleled comfort and style, keeping your legs cozy throughout the season.
<ul>
 	<li>* 100% Wool</li>
 	<li>* Enduring Style</li>
 	<li>* Easy to Care for</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Step into the embrace of comfort and style with the &#8220;Winter Whisper&#8221; knitted wool legwarmers. Expertly crafted with the finest wool, these legwarmers offer a luxurious and cozy experience like no other. The intricate knitted design showcases exquisite craftsmanship, adding a touch of elegance to your winter ensemble. The soft and insulating wool material provides exceptional warmth, ensuring your legs stay snug even on the coldest days. With their stretchy yet secure fit, the &#8220;Winter Whisper&#8221; legwarmers stay in place, allowing you to move with freedom and grace. Whether you&#8217;re enjoying a cozy night by the fire or heading out for a winter adventure, these legwarmers are the perfect accessory to keep you stylishly warm throughout the season. Indulge in the whisper of winter with these exquisite, knitted wool legwarmers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/winter-whisper-legwarmer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cozy Bliss Legwarmer</title>
		<link>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-bliss-legwarmer/</link>
					<comments>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-bliss-legwarmer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 08:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/?post_type=product#038;p=158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Luxurious knitted wool legwarmers that embrace your legs with warmth, style, and unparalleled comfort.
<ul>
 	<li>* Authentic Product</li>
 	<li>* Cozy and Insulating</li>
 	<li>* Stylish and Versatile</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Indulge in the warmth and comfort of the &#8220;Cozy Bliss&#8221; knitted wool legwarmers. Crafted with meticulous care and adorned with intricate patterns, these legwarmers are the epitome of cozy elegance. Made from the finest quality wool, they embrace your legs with a gentle embrace, shielding them from the chill of winter while adding a touch of style to any outfit. The soft, plush texture of the knitted wool creates a heavenly cocoon around your calves, offering a luxurious sensation with every step. With their stretchy yet snug fit, these legwarmers stay securely in place without compromising on flexibility. Unleash the power of comfort and fashion with &#8220;Cozy Bliss&#8221; legwarmers, an essential accessory for both chilly nights in and fashionable outings.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jeenakarmi.github.io/OoniBunai/product/cozy-bliss-legwarmer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
